All roads lead to the truth.
Retribution is a thriller, action, adventure film directed by Nimród Antal.
When a mysterious caller plants a bomb under his car seat, a bank executive begins a high-speed chase across
the city to complete a specific series of tasks — all with his kids trapped in the back seat.
Matt Turner, played by Liam Neeson.
Emily Turner, played by Lilly Aspell.
Zach Turner, played by Jack Champion.
Anders Muller, played by Matthew Modine.
Angela Brickmann, played by Noma Dumezweni.
Heather Turner, played by Embeth Davidtz.
Retribution is a 2023 action thriller film directed by
Nimród Antal and written by Chris Salmanpour.
The film stars Liam Neeson, Noma Dumezweni, Lilly Aspell, Jack
Champion, Embeth Davidtz and Matthew Modine.
It is the third remake of the 2015 Spanish film El desconocido, which follows a man (Neeson) who
gets trapped in his car after receiving a threat that it will explode if he gets out.
An international co-production of France, Germany, Spain and the United States, Retribution was released in France on
August 23, 2023 by StudioCanal, and in the United States on August 25 by Lionsgate and Roadside Attractions.
The film explores themes of berlin, germany,
assassination, bomb, remake, divorce.
The tone is intense.